A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 3
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 742)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 743)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1978 (Box 54, Folder 744)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1926-1949 (Box 54, Folder 745)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Minutes - Board of Trustees; Executive and Finance Committees, 1927-1948 (Box 54, Folder 746)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Minutes - Board of Trustees; Executive and Finance Committees, 1927-1948 (Box 54, Folder 747)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1929-1935 (Box 54, Folder 748)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1929-1935 (Box 54, Folder 749)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 750)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 751)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 752)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 753)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 754)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 755)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 756)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 757)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Monthly Reports, 1936-1949 (Box 55, Folder 758)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1932 (Box 55, Folder 759)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1932 (Box 55, Folder 760)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1939 (Box 56, Folder 761)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1933; 1936-1939 (Box 56, Folder 762)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Public Health Program - Financial Correspondence and Vouchers, 1929-1938 (Box 56, Folder 763)
  - Glasgow, Kentucky - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1948 (Box 56, Folder 764)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Annual Report, September 30, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 765)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Audit Reports, 1934-1935, 1940-1942, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 766)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Audit Reports, 1934-1935, 1940-1942, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 767)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Bids and Pre-Qualification Statements, December 6-9, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 768)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Agreements, 1932-1940 (Box 56, Folder 769)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Change Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 770)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 771)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 772)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 773)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 774)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Purchase Orders, 1935-1937 (Box 56, Folder 775)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Community Hospital Services - Accounting Manual, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 776)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Community Hospital Services - General Manual, 1942; 1948 (Box 57, Folder 777)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1934-1947 (Box 57, Folder 778)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1934-1947 (Box 57, Folder 779)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1934-1947 (Box 57, Folder 780)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1934-1947 (Box 57, Folder 781)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Bids-New Wing, 1940-1941 (Box 57, Folder 782)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 783)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 784)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 785)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 786)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1934-1942 (Box 57, Folder 787)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders (Pre-Opening), 1934-1935 (Box 57, Folder 788)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1934-1935; 1938; 1941 (Box 58, Folder 789)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1934-1935; 1938; 1941 (Box 58, Folder 790)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1934-1935; 1938; 1941 (Box 58, Folder 791)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1934-1935; 1938; 1941 (Box 58, Folder 792)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1934-1941 (Box 58, Folder 793)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Fellowships (B-D), 1934-1946 (Box 58, Folder 794)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Fellowships (E-Q), 1934-1946 (Box 58, Folder 795)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 58, Folder 796)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 58, Folder 797)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 58, Folder 798)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 58, Folder 799)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1933-1947 (Box 58, Folder 800)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1933 (Box 58, Folder 801)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 802)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 803)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 804)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 805)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 806)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 807)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 808)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 809)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 810)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 811)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 812)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 813)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 814)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 815)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 816)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 817)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 818)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 819)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1969 (Box 60, Folder 820)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1928-1951 (Box 60, Folder 821)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1928-1951 (Box 60, Folder 822)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1933-1936 (Box 60, Folder 823)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1933-1936 (Box 60, Folder 824)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1933-1936 (Box 60, Folder 825)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1933-1936 (Box 60, Folder 826)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 827)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 828)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 829)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 830)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 831)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 832)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 833)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 834)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 835)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 836)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 837)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Director, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 838)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1935-1937 (Box 61, Folder 839)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1935-1937 (Box 61, Folder 840)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1935-1937 (Box 61, Folder 841)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 842)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 843)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 844)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 845)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 846)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 847)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 849)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 850)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1938-1947 (Box 62, Folder 851)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 852)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1940 (Box 63, Folder 853)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1940 (Box 63, Folder 854)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1940 (Box 63, Folder 855)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 856)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 857)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 858)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 859)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 860)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 861)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 862)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1933-1936 (Box 63, Folder 863)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 864)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 865)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 866)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 867)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 868)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 869)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 870)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 871)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 872)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 873)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 874)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 875)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 876)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 877)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 64, Folder 878)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 879)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 880)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 881)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 882)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 883)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1933-1949 (Box 65, Folder 884)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Forms and Contracts, 1941-1942; 1944 and 1948 (Box 65, Folder 885)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Forms and Contracts, 1941-1942; 1944 and 1948 (Box 65, Folder 886)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Forms and Contracts, 1941-1942; 1944 and 1948 (Box 65, Folder 887)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Hospital Service Plan Commission, 1942-1944 (Box 65, Folder 888)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Inter-Plan Service-Benefit Bank (Analysis), 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 889)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Inter-Plan Service-Benefit Bank (Statistical Report), April 1947 (Box 65, Folder 890)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Manual of Uniform Accounting Procedures, August 1943 (Box 65, Folder 891)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Pamphlets, 1944 and 1946 (Box 65, Folder 892)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Publicity - Brochures for Holston Valley Community Hospital and Kingston, Tennessee, 1933-1947 (Box 66, Folder 893)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Report - Committee on Accounting and Office Practice to the Conference of Hospital Service Plans, February 1941 (Box 66, Folder 894)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Report - Committee on Hospital and Medical Relations of the American Hospital Association, Council on Hospital Service Plans, February 1941 (Box 66, Folder 895)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Report - Committee on Rural Development to American Hospital Association, Council on Hospital Service Plans, February 1941 (Box 66, Folder 896)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Report - Foundations of the Holston Valley Community Hospital, April 1949 (Box 66, Folder 897)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Report - Rehabilitation Services in the Kingsport, Tennessee Area, May 1954 (Box 66, Folder 898)
  - Kingsport, Tennessee - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1935-1948 (Box 66, Folder 899)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Audit Report, 1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 900)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1939-1941 (Box 66, Folder 901)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Change and Purchase Orders, 1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 902)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1939-1942 (Box 66, Folder 903)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1939-1942 (Box 66, Folder 904)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1939-1942 (Box 66, Folder 905)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1939-1942 (Box 66, Folder 906)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data, 1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 907)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 908)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 909)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 910)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Disbursements, 1939-1949 (Box 67, Folder 911)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1939-1941 (Box 67, Folder 912)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1939-1941 (Box 67, Folder 913)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1939-1941 (Box 67, Folder 914)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Purchase Orders (Pre-Opening), 1940 (Box 67, Folder 915)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1938-1939 (Box 67, Folder 916)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1938-1939 (Box 67, Folder 917)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1939-1941 (Box 68, Folder 918)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Fellowships (B-P), 1939-1941 (Box 68, Folder 919)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 68, Folder 920)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 68, Folder 921)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Field Trip Memoranda, 1938-1947 (Box 68, Folder 922)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 923)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 924)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 925)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 926)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 927)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 928)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 929)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 930)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 931)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 932)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 933)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 934)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 935)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 936)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 937)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 938)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1949-1961 (Box 70, Folder 939)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1937-1951 (Box 70, Folder 940)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Medical Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 70, Folder 941)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Medical Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 70, Folder 942)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Medical Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 70, Folder 943)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Minutes - Executive Committee; Board of Directors and Members, 1939-1952 (Box 70, Folder 944)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Minutes - Executive Committee; Board of Directors and Members, 1939-1952 (Box 70, Folder 945)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1939-1944 (Box 70, Folder 946)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1939-1944 (Box 70, Folder 947)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1939-1944 (Box 70, Folder 948)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1939-1944 (Box 70, Folder 949)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 950)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 951)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 952)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 953)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 954)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 955)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Monthly Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 71, Folder 956)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Nurse Education Program - Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 71, Folder 957)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1943 (Box 71, Folder 958)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, April-October, 1947 (Box 71, Folder 959)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Public Health Program - Memoranda, May 15-17, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 960)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Publicity - Articles and Brochures, 1937-1947 (Box 71, Folder 961)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Site Selection Data, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 962)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Site Selection Data, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 963)
  - Lancaster, South Carolina - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1939-1948 (Box 71, Folder 964)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Audit Reports, 1941-1943; December 31, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 965)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1941-1942 (Box 72, Folder 966)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Change Orders, 1941-1943 (Box 72, Folder 967)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1941-1946 (Box 72, Folder 968)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1941-1946 (Box 72, Folder 969)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1941-1946 (Box 72, Folder 970)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1941-1946 (Box 72, Folder 971)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Extra Building Contracts, January-July, 1943 (Box 72, Folder 972)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Building Requisitions - Pre-Qualification Statements, March-April, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 973)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Disbursements, 1942-1948 (Box 72, Folder 974)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Budget Data Sheets, August 1942 (Box 72, Folder 975)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 976)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 977)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 978)